The Flight of the Grey Wolf is a adventure, drama,
family film directed by Frank Zuniga.
A youth (Russ Hanson) attempts to re-introduce a domesticated wolf to the wild.
Russ Hanson, played by Jeff East.
The Sheriff, played by Bill Williams.
Mrs Hanson, played by Barbara Hale.
Mr Hanson, played by William Bryant.
The Flight of the Grey Wolf was a 1976 television film produced by Walt Disney Productions, and
broadcast in two parts on The Wonderful World of Disney, the first part airing on May 14, 1976.
The film was directed by Frank Zuniga, and stars Jeff East,
Bill Williams, Barbara Hale, and William Bryant.
In July 1975 Disney announced that the film would be part of its
1975-1976 line-up on The Wonderful World of Disney.
It was to be one of two longer films which were to be broken down into two parts and be
shown on back-to-back Sundays, the other being The Boy Who Talked to Badgers.
The first part of the film aired on Sunday, March 14, 1976,
opposite The Wizard of Oz, which was airing on CBS.
The second part aired the following Sunday, March 21.
The tone is emotional.